♪〜
〜♪
（クリフ）また やつか
何とかしなければ…
Him again.
Something has to be done.
このままでは…
He has to be stopped!
（荒い息づかい）
Ma'am, I don't see a soul.
（ミリィ･トンプソン）
先輩　人っ子一人 見当たりません
（メリル･ストライフ）この町が
ゴーストタウンになったなんて—
No one told me this town
had become a ghost town.
聞いていませんでしたわ
I hope there's a well somewhere...
どこかに井戸でもあれば…
Wishful thinking will only
make the truth more painful.
希望的観測を口にすると
現実がつらくなりまして…
（メリルとミリィ）ああっ！
（弾む息）
うわー！
あああっ！
うひゃー！
（おけが底に落ちた音）
The truth hurts.
（ミリィ）
現実がつらいですね
同感ですわ
I agree.
あっ
Land sinkage?
地盤沈下？
（親）ああ なんてこったい！
Land sakes!
水がかれた上に—
First the water dries up and then
the legendary outlaw shows up!
伝説の賞金首が
やってくるなんてよお
（子）
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードが—
Yeah, Vash the Stampede,
a hired gun at Mr. Schezar's mansion!
セザールさんの屋敷の
用心棒をするんだよね
This town is finished!
（親）この町も終わりだ
（子）あーらら 大変だ ♪
Oh, it's the end of the world...
...the e-e-end of the world!
ええっ？
- Ma'am!
- Finally...
先輩
ついに…
Finally!
ついに！
We can get water
from that mansion!
そのお屋敷で
水を分けてもらいましょう
No, not that.
いや そうでなくって…
（ノックする音）
Excuse me, is this
the Schezar residence?
（メリル）すみません
セザールさんのお宅ですか？
I'm Meryl Stryfe, disaster investigator
for the Bernardelli Insurance Society.
私(わたくし) ベルナルデリ保険協会の
災害調査員—
メリル･ストライフと申します
I'm Milly Thompson!
（ミリィ）
同じく ミリィ･トンプソンです
I'm very thirsty!
喉が渇いております
Don't say that!
あっ じゃなくて…
We heard that Vash the Stampede
was staying here.
こちらのお宅に—
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードが
いると聞いて—
やってきたのですが…
（メリル）おおっ
（ミリィ）ああっ
ああ ごちそうさまでした
Thank you!
We really appreciate this!
ホントに助かりましたわ
（ミリィ･メリル）あっ
Hello!
（ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード）
どうも〜
Hello!
どうも
なんで あなたが
ここにいるんですの？
What are you doing here?
I'm Mr. Cliff's hired
bodyguard, ace gunman!
私がクリフさんの用心棒に雇われた
すご腕ガンマンです
あっ それ手土産ですか？
Is that for me?
ウフフッ
すいませんね もう…
Hey, thanks!
あなたが用心棒？
You, a bodyguard?
んんっ　そうだよ
Yup.
“そうだよ”って…
Yup?!
We meet again, Mr. Ace Gunman!
また お会いしましたね
すご腕ガンマンさん
ホント奇遇だね　ハハッ
It's an amazing coincidence!
These are really good!
うん いけるよ これ
うんうんっ
食べる？ あんた　ん？
Want one?
はい！ いただきまーす
Yes, I'd love one!!
Stop the irrelevant chatter, Milly.
トンチキな会話しないで ミリィ
はあ？
What's your real reason
for being here?!
あなたがここにいる
本当の理由は何ですの？
にゅ〜
That's an odd response.
妙なリアクションですわね
（クリフ）フッ フッフッフッ…
Are these young ladies...
そこにいるお嬢さん方は—
ヴァッシュさんの
お知り合いですか？
...friends of yours, Vash?
ヴァッシュ？
VASH? He's not...
こここ… この男
In any event, you seem
to be here for a reason.
（クリフ）
何やら 事情がおありのようだ
えっ？
（クリフ）
こんな所で立ち話もなんですから
中へお入りください
We shouldn't discuss it out here.
Please come in.
Uh, we're...
（メリル）ああ いえ あの…
（蓄音機から聞こえる音楽）
I am Cliff Schezar.
私はクリフ･セザール
I make a living
selling water in this town...
この町で水を売って
なりわいとしているんですが
...but recently someone's
been trying to kill me.
最近 何者かに狙われておりまして
So I advertised
for a good bodyguard.
腕の立つ用心棒を
募集してたんですよ
For someone good and tough,
like Vash the Stampede.
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
みたいな 強い男をね
Oh.
はあ
I originally wrote it as a joke.
冗談で書いたつもりでしたが
I never dreamed the
real thing would show up.
いやいや
まさか本物が来てくれるとは—
思いもよらぬ偶然でした
ねえ？ ヴァッシュさん
Eh, Vash?
ううっ
ええ
Yes. Now that I am here,
you have nothing to fear.
僕が来たからには もう安心ですよ
群がる善人を撃ち倒し—
Merciless slayer
of all that is good!
Doer of the evil, evil deeds a man
with $ $60 billion on his head does!
悪行のかぎりを尽くす
600億ダブドルの賞金首といえば—
That's me!
この僕のことですよ　にゅっ
He's such a nice, dependable guy.
なんとも頼りになりそうな
ナイスガイですな
ハハハハッ
これで このお屋敷の人も
安心して暮らせますね
Now the people in
this mansion will feel safe!
（メリル）ぐっ
失礼ですけど
あなたの目は多分に節穴…
This may sound rude,
but you need your eyes checked!
聞いてください
Hear me out. I desperately
needed a good bodyguard.
私には どうしても
腕の立つ用心棒が必要だったのです
Her name is Marianne Aura Cayzen.
彼女の名前は
マリアンヌ･オーレルカイゼン
Granddaughter of the director
of the Stantal Federal Bureau...
スタンタル連邦支局長の
お孫さんで—
客人として 私の屋敷に
滞在していらっしゃいます
...and a guest at my home.
The truth is, someone attempted
to break in here 5 days ago.
実は ５日前にも
何者かが
屋敷に侵入しようとしてきました
（マリアンヌ）ウフッ
ん？
（ヴァッシュのにやけた声）
うわっ
I wouldn't hire a bodyguard
if I were the only one in danger...
（クリフ）
私が狙われるくらいなら—
用心棒など
雇うつもりはないんですが
...but I want to avoid
anything happening to her.
彼女に危害が及ぶのだけは
どうしても避けたい
だからこそ
あなたの力が必要なのです
That is why I need your help.
You can count on me, Mr. Cliff.
任せておいてください
クリフさん
ぐっ
I don't let anyone
in my sights get away...
（ヴァッシュ）
僕は狙った獲物を逃がさないし
...and my bullets
never miss their mark.
撃った弾(たま)を外したこともない
Especially if it's the heart
of a beautiful lady.
特に 美しい女性のハートはね
Bang!
バーン！
うおー！
（ヴァッシュ）ん？
Ma'am!
先輩
さ… さすが ヴァッシュ様
頼もしいわ
l-I know I can
depend on you, Mr. Vash.
A lot of people say that!
い… いやあ
よく言われるんですけどね
そうですか 言われますか
I see. Do they now?
アッハッハッハッ…
はい　いや もう しょっちゅう
Yeah, all the time!
ハハハハッ アハハハッ…
Ma'am! Ma'am!
先輩 先輩
あっ
Come here for a moment.
ちょっと こっちへ
What's the matter?
どうしました？
Mr. Cliff, listen very carefully.
ミスター･クリフ
よーく聞いてください
Does that man look like the
legendary gunman, Vash the Stampede?!
あの男が伝説のガンマン—
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードに
見えますか？
That droopy-eyed,
weak-looking, bristle-headed...
あんなに垂れ目で 貧弱そうで
髪 逆立てて—
...promiscuous-looking
donut freak of a man?!
女に節操がなさそうで
ドーナツに目がないような男が！
She bought the donuts.
ドーナツは
先輩が買ってきたんじゃ…
And we can hear every word.
（ヴァッシュ）
しかも 会話 筒抜け
ズバリ！ あなたは
あの男に だまされてますわ
I'm saying you're being
deceived by that man!
だましているのは私のほうです
I'm the one doing the deceiving.
えっ？
You saw the town.
町の様子を見たでしょう？
All it took was the rumor that
my bodyguard was Vash the Stampede.
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードが—
私の用心棒になったという
うわさだけで あのとおりです
The rabble after me
will panic just as much.
ならば 私を狙っているやからも
同じことを考えるはずです
Afternoon!
Your ad caught my eye!
ちわっ！ チラシ見たんすけど…
Congratulations!
You are now Vash the Stampede!
やあ　あなたは今日から
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードです
Wha'?
はあ？
Hello, Vash the Stampede!
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードです
Anybody would have done.
要は 誰でもよかったんですよ
I see. It's a huge inconvenience,
but your plan is very clear to me now.
なるほど
はた迷惑ですけど—
あなたのお考えは
よく分かりました
Originally, I didn't
want it to go this far...
本来なら ここまでは
したくなかったんですが
...but the man after me is
a blond packing a silver weapon...
私を狙ってきた人物は
金髪で銀色の武器を持った—
...and he's quite the ace!
相当な すご腕なんです
えっ？
Did you hear, Milly?
聞きまして？ ミリィ
Yes, every word!!
（ミリィ）ええ
バッチリ エビチリですね
This is an unbelievable windfall!
棚からぼた餅ですわよ
They really are delightful.
愉快な方たちですわね
It's best not to burst
the bubble of an airhead.
脳天気は ほうっておくが吉です
Mr. Cliff! If you don't mind,
please let us be your bodyguards too!
クリフさん
よろしければ 私たちも
用心棒に加えさせてください
Naturally, we won't demand a fee
like that greedy faker over there!
もちろん あそこにいる
無遠慮な偽物とは違って—
報酬をよこせなんて
言いませんわ
（クリフ）
フフフッ かまいませんよ
That's fine by me.
Thank you, sir!
（メリル）ありがとうございます
これが用心棒の仕事なんですの？
Is this what bodyguards do?
Every great journey must begin
with a single enormous step.
“千里の道も
九十九里を行くがごとし”ですね
Is it ready yet?
メシ まだ？
We will serve up shortly.
今 持っていきますわよ
Ooh, scary. Later.
ううっ こわっ
ほな
Nothing has gone right
since we met him.
まったく あの男と出会ってから
ろくなことがありませんわ
Really? I'm having
a wonderful time!
（ミリィ）ええ？
私 結構 楽しいですよ こういうの
And we get all
the water we want!
水も飲み放題だし
（メリル）だっ
She's so short-tempered.
（ヴァッシュ）
まったく 短気なお姉ちゃんだねえ
（水が流れる音）
The sound of water
rings in my ear.
聞こえてくる 水の音
And the room next
to me is Marianne's.
そして
隣はマリアンヌちゃんの部屋
Lifeline secure!
命綱 よし！
Wind, favorable!
The plan is perfect.
風向き よし！
作戦 完璧
Guts, steeled!
度胸も よし！
にや〜
I'm coming, Marianne!
マリアンヌちゃん 今 行くよー！
なっ
（ノックする音）
Miss Marianne, supper is ready!
（ミリィ）マリアンヌさん
お食事の準備が…
Huh?
あれ？
ん？
Hello!
どうも
ハア…
こんな所で何してるんですか？
What are you doing out there?
い… いや
ちょっと屋根につく悪霊を—
O-Oh, I'm diligently patrolling
the roof for evil spooks.
鋭意 パトロール中
うわあ 怖いですね
That sounds scary!
Bodyguards sure are busy people!
用心棒って大変なんだ
Oh, yeah! Supper's ready!
あっ お食事の準備
出来てますから
アハッ　ありがとう
Thanks.
（ドアが開く音）
（メリル）あっ
This is Mr. Cliff's study.
ここはミスター･クリフの書斎
マリアンヌさん？
Miss Marianne?
（ヴァッシュ）
しかし 豪華ですよね
This place sure is fancy!
Is water that profitable?
水って
そんなに もうかるんですか？
We've had a drought for
the past several years.
（クリフ）
ここ数年 日照り続きですからね
I'm able to enjoy a few
luxuries because my father...
…で 今 私が—
ささやかなぜいたくを
させてもらっているのも
...who was a plant engineer,
purchased land with a water supply.
プラント技師だった父が—
水源のある土地を
買ってくれていた おかげなんです
羨む人が たくさんいそうですね
I bet a lot of people are jealous.
Yes, the rabble who
are after the rights.
そうです
利権を求めるやからです
They probably think
I'm monopolizing the water.
彼らは—
私が水を独占しているとでも
考えているんでしょう
But I have something to say to them.
ですが 私の言い分もあります
Water is not limitless. Unless it
is managed properly, it will dry up.
水は無限ではありません
計画的に採らないと
すぐに干上がってしまう
（マリアンヌ）でも…
But it doesn't change the fact you're
profiting from a natural resource.
自然をお金で売っていることに
変わりはありませんわ
I'm sorry, it's not my business.
すいません よけいなことを…
No, you're quite right.
（クリフ）
いえいえ そのとおりですよ
だが 心ない者たちに
水を奪われるわけにはいかない
But I can't let the water
be stolen by thoughtless people.
They may call me a coward,
but I intend to protect the water.
ひきょう者と罵られようが
私は水を守るつもりです
すばらしいお考えですね
That's very admirable!
（イスが動く音）
（ヴァッシュ）ん？
ミスター･クリフ
Mr. Cliff, I don't feel well.
Please excuse me.
気分がすぐれないので
失礼させていただきます
ああ…
（クリフ）
しっかりしてそうに見えて
不安なんでしょう
She may look calm,
but she's probably ill at ease.
あ？
I probably shouldn't
have invited her here.
やはり ここへ来させるべきでは
なかったようだ
（ヴァッシュ）は… はあ
I see. Well, I think
I'll go make the rounds!
さてと ちょっと見回ってきます
I can at least act
like a real bodyguard.
飾りの用心棒でも—
少しは らしくしといたほうが
いいですからね
I've instructed Marianne
to keep her curtain drawn.
マリアンヌには—
窓にカーテンをかけるように
言ってありますよ
えっ いや…
Oh, please!
I would never dream of...
ヤ… ヤダなあ 誰がそんなこと？
おおっ
いえいえ 何が言いたいのか
理解不能ですよ
I mean, I cannot comprehend
what you are implying.
アッハッハッハッ
ほな
Later.
んん…
I'm exhausted from all that cooking.
（ミリィ）
なんか どっと疲れましたね
メシ炊き
We're just getting started.
We never know when he'll show up.
仕事は これからですわ
相手が いつ現れるか
分からないんですから
There will be no sleep tonight.
今夜は眠れませんわよ
（メリル･ミリィ）あむっ
If it's not him, this has
been a nuclear waste of time.
これで人違いだったら
メガトン ムダ足ですよね
（ヴァッシュ）入っていいですか？
May I come in?
（マリアンヌ）
あっ　少しお待ちください
Just a minute!
どうぞ
Come in!
Excuse me.
（ヴァッシュ）失礼します
（マリアンヌ）えっ？
Is something wrong?
（ヴァッシュ）どうしました？
（マリアンヌ）あっ い… いえ
Er, no!
Were you gazing at the stars?
（ヴァッシュ）
星を眺めていたんですか？
Y-Yes.
え… ええ
I was thinking of home...
少し 故郷のことを考えてました
...even though none of
the thoughts were pleasant.
いい思い出なんか
全然ありませんのに…
Thoughts of home are proof
of a journey of the heart.
故郷を思い出すってことは
心が旅をしている証拠ですよ
あっ はあ…
I actually wanted to travel
by myself here and there...
ホントは 気ままな一人旅を
楽しみたかったんですけど
...but I couldn't persuade my father.
お父様が納得してくれなくて…
So, I go from house to house,
staying with his friends.
それで お父様の知人の家を
転々としてるんです
ウフフッ
This is hardly
what I call a journey.
こんなもの
旅でも何でもありませんわね
あっ あ… あの…
Um...
あっ
ううっ　く…
いつか 本当の旅ができる日が
きっと来ますよ
Someday you will be able
to go on a real journey.
Although it may
not be a lone one.
一人旅じゃ
ないかもしれないけど
あら？
Oh, but what do you mean by that?
それは どういう意味でしょうか？
うっ
あっ 今 何か動きましたわ
I saw something move!
えっ？
（マリアンヌ）ほら また
There it is again!
（ヴァッシュ）んん…
Stand back, I'll go look.
下がって　僕が見てきます
（マリアンヌ）でも…
- But...
- It's my job.
それが仕事ですから
（ヴァッシュ）フッ
Dammit!
クッソー！
That hurt, you oaf!
痛いじゃないの！ バカ
（ヴァッシュ）フッ
（メリル）うわー！
Stay still!
（ヴァッシュ）おとなしくしろ！
キャーッ！ 出ましたわよ！
Eek! He's here!
It's Vash the Stampede!!
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードが
現れましたわー！
放しなさい！
訴えてやりますわ… よ？
Let go of me, or I'll sue...
...you?
あっ あなた
何しようとしてるんですの？
Hey, what are you doing to me?!
Aw, it's just you.
なんだ 君か
What do you mean, "just" me?!
“なんだ”とは何ですのよ？
I wanted to chew out
whoever interrupted...
“マリアンヌちゃんとの
実りある未来”という—
...my debate of
a fructuous future with Marianne.
テーマでの議論を邪魔したやつを
懲らしめに来たのに…
私が何したっていうんですか？
So what did I do?!
Besides, do you really
have a clean conscience?
それに ホントにやましい気持ちは
ないんですの？
Not where Marianne is concerned...
マリアンヌちゃんには 少し…
I had no idea you two
were so friendly, ma'am.
先輩たち いつの間に
そんなに仲良くなったんですか？
Have you been paying attention?!
人の話 聞いてなかったの？
Miss Marianne,
don't worry your little head!
マリアンヌさーん
安心してくださーい
I caught the culprit!
怪しいやつは捕まえましたよー！
Who are you calling a culprit?
だから 誰が怪しいって？
あれ？
Nuh?
- Anything?
- Not a trace.
（メリル）どうでした？
（ヴァッシュ）さっぱり…
What's going on? Both Miss Marianne
and Mr. Cliff are missing.
（メリル）どういうことですの？
マリアンヌさんだけでなく—
ミスター･クリフまで
屋敷にいないなんて…
まさか さらわれたとか…
You think they were kidnapped?!
We were outside the entire time.
That's impossible.
外には私たちがいましたのよ
そんなはずないわ
I'm so worried!
あーあ 心配だな
Ma'am, they're nowhere to be found!
（ミリィ）
先輩　どこにもいませんよ
What's that?
（メリル）それは？
Miss Marianne's dress
and some bandages.
（ミリィ）
マリアンヌさんのドレスと
包帯です
An attempted break-in
5 days ago...
５日前に
屋敷に侵入しようとした人物
A discarded dress
and bloody bandages...
脱ぎ捨てられたドレスに
血の付いた包帯
Miss Marianne entering
Mr. Cliff's study...
ミスター･クリフの書斎にいた
マリアンヌさん
That's more than enough
circumstantial evidence.
状況証拠は十分すぎるほど
そろってますわね
You're wrong!!
（ヴァッシュ）ちがーう！
（メリル）ん？
Marianne isn't that kind of girl!
マリアンヌちゃんは
そんな子じゃなーい！
How can you be so sure?
（メリル）
どうして そう言い切れるの？
Ahem.
ゴホン
I can tell.
Marianne has a beautiful heart.
僕には分かるんだ
マリアンヌちゃんは
心のキレイな子だって
You're the easily deceived type
who sleeps on a tear-soaked pillow.
女にだまされ
涙で枕をぬらすタイプですわね
Dream wrecker.
チッ　人の夢を…
あっ そうだ
きっと神隠しですよ
I know! A ghost got her!
（ヴァッシュとメリル）はあ？
You said yourself there
were evil spooks on the roof.
“屋根に悪霊が出る”って
言ってたじゃないですか？
いっ あっ いや
それはその…
Uh, that was...
Er...
えっ ええと その…　うがっ
（メリル）え？
（ヴァッシュ）いや 霊というか…
By spooks, I meant...
- What's this about the roof?
- Well, actually, etc, etc...
By spooks, I meant...
（メリル）何があったんですの？
（ミリィ）
実は かくかくしかじか…
というわけです
- What's this about the roof?
- Well, actually, etc, etc...
...you know...
HEY!
あなた！
Yes, ma'am!!
はい！
What were you doing
peeking into a lady's room?!
女性の部屋をのぞくなんて
どういう了見ですの？
Wait, time out!
ちょ ちょ ちょ…
ちょっと タンマ タンマ！
事と次第によっては
容赦しませんことよ！
Whatever you've done,
you won't get away with it!
あっ タンマ タンマ タンマって
言ってんのに…
Time out, I said! Time out!
ああっ
あ？ あうっ
（３人）あっ
I thought as much.
やっぱり こういうことだったのね
Such a naughty little princess!
（クリフ）
まったく ヤンチャなお姫様だ
あっ
Even pranks have a limit.
いたずらにも程がある
ん？
フンッ
So they've started recruiting kids?
お上(かみ)も最近は
ガキを使いによこすのか
Thanks to your
monopolization of the water...
（マリアンヌ）
あなたが水を独占したせいで
この辺りの土地は全滅したわ
...the land in this area is all dead!
Do you know how many people
have suffered because of you?!
そのために どれだけの人が
苦しんだと思っているの？
And so you came to get proof?
それで
証拠をつかみに来たってわけか
Cheap sense of justice.
安っぽい正義感だ
（マリアンヌ）うっ あ…
Oh, that's right...
（クリフ）ああ そうだったね
I shot you.
撃たれてたんだよな！
（マリアンヌ）うおっ
うっ
The townspeople have all fled
so there will be no witnesses.
住民は避難してて
目撃者が出ることもない
（マリアンヌ）おっ　あ…
I was right to spread the
rumor of Vash the Stampede.
（クリフ）
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピードの
うわさを—
流したかいがあったってもんだ
ううっ う…
An investment must always pay off.
Do you think I'd let this ruin me?
投資した分は
回収しなくっちゃならない
こんな所で つまずけるか！
Game over.
ゲームオーバーだ
（ヴァッシュ）ひょげ〜！
（マリアンヌ）あっ
（クリフ）ん？
フハハッ　大丈夫？
You okay?
Oaf.
バカ
（メリル）何が
“俺様が背後に回り込む”よ
Is that what he meant by
sneaking up from behind?!
Now it's gone from
pinch to overflow.
ピンチが
オーバーフローしてますね
Really! We can't
lift a finger now!
まったく あの状況じゃ
手出しできませんわよ
あっ
That explains your little luxuries.
なるほど
ぜいたくできるわけだ
チッ　手間を増やしやがって！
Wasting more of my time!
Run, quickly!
逃げなさい！ 早く！
あああっ
Thank goodness!
よかった
You're the girl
I thought you were!!
思ってたとおりの女の子だ
あ…
フンッ　勇敢だな
Very brave.
（銃声）
あっ
（ミリィとメリル）あっ
はっ
わっ
YEEK!
こわー！
クッソー！
Damn.
だあっ　おっ
えっ　はっ　わっ
おっ　危ない
はっ　ほっ　危ない
こ… こいつ
銃の向きとタイミングで—
What, is he predicting my shots
through gun movements and timing?
弾道を予測してるってのか？
（ヴァッシュ）はっ？
はあっ
No, you're a bad shot.
ヘタっぴなの
（クリフ）おわっ
W-Who the hell are you?
なっ な… 何なんだ？ 貴様
I'm your ace bodyguard.
あんたに雇われた
すご腕の用心棒さ
フフフッ　やるじゃないか
Not bad.
I was right when I chose to hire you.
あんたを選んだ俺の目に
狂いは なかったようだ
Don't you agree?
そうだろ？
ん？
ふっ！
うわあっ
（銃声）
うっ　貴様！
You!
I've protected your guest,
as requested.
依頼どおり
あんたの客人は守ったぜ
あっ あれ…
Look!
へっ？
You're kidding!!
ウソー！
We did it, ma'am!
やりましたね 先輩
Now is not the time
to say that!!
そんなこと言ってる場合じゃ
ありませんわよー！
（トマの鳴き声）
It's all right. The dammed water
overflowed all at once, that's all.
大丈夫
せき止められた水が
一気にあふれ出ただけだもの
It will return underground
and make the town prosper again.
また 地下水に戻って
町に恵みを与えてくれる
出ていったみんなも
また きっと戻ってくるわ
I'm sure everyone
who left will return.
Thanks.
ありがとう
Aw, shucks!
いやあ
It was just a series
of incredibly dumb luck.
すごーくラッキーな偶然が
重なっただけですわよ
Was that bullet-dodging also luck,
or did you plan it that way?
じゃあ あの弾を避けたのも偶然？
それとも わざとかしら？
It was more like a fluke.
どっちかっちゅうと
まぐれのほうかな
ウフッ　意識的にやったんなら
本気で信じちゃうわ
If you knew what you were doing,
I'd be convinced...
あなたが
...that you are Vash the Stampede.
ヴァッシュ･ザ･スタンピード
だってこと
えっ？
And if I was?
ホントにそうだとしたら？
I'd arrest you.
捕まえるわ
フッ
I have to thank you as well.
（マリアンヌ）
あなたたちも ありがとう
You must be glad your job is done.
仕事が終わって よかったですわね
こっちは進展なしですわよ
We're still at square one!
Don't let it get to you, ma'am.
ドンマイですよ 先輩
あっ
Are you going?
もう行くの？
My work here is done.
（ヴァッシュ）
仕事が終わったからね
The nameless bodyguard.
名無しの用心棒さんか…
He isn't bad.
A girl could fall for him.
いい男じゃない？
ホレちゃいそう
えっ どうして？
What?! But he's so irresponsible!
あんな いいかげんな男ですのに…
You have no eye for men.
あなた 見る目がないわね
Says who?!
（メリル）どっちが！
Someday, you'll see.
そのうち 分かるようになるわよ
I'd rather not see, thank you!
絶対に分かりたくないですわよ
そんなの
ドンマイですよ 先輩
Don't let it get to you, ma'am!
（ヴァッシュ）あーあ
I was so sure it'd work out.
ウマくいくと思ったんだけどな…
She was such a cutie...
かわいかったんだけどな
...but it wouldn't work out.
I don't wanna be arrested.
ダメだよな
捕まるのヤダしな
This one will probably
be blamed on me, too.
今回の事件も
俺のせいにされちゃうんだろうな
Aw, man!
ヤダな
あーあ
♪〜
〜♪
Those who made mistakes blame
themselves and close their hearts.
（ヴァッシュ）過ちを犯した者は
自らを責め 心を閉ざす
過ちを正すことはできない
It's impossible to fix the mistake.
Man can't return to the past.
人は過去には戻れない
That's why we drink. Drunks, lushes,
sliding alcohol down their throats...
だから 飲む
飲んだくれ 酔っ払い
偽っても隠せない思いを酒で薄め
喉に流し込む
...to dilute the memories
that can't be denied.
Frank Marlon the gunsmith
does nothing but drink.
銃職人 フランク･マーロンは
ただ酒を飲む
And he questions
the drained glass, "Am I wrong?"
そして
空になったグラスに問いかける
俺は間違っているのか？
"Was I wrong?"
俺は間違っていたのか？